http://ormsby.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Product Search
Search for:
Search
Cart
About UsMeet the TeamContact UsMy accountView Cart
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThis section covers the following:Use of your Personal InformationFraud PreventionDisclosure of Your Information SecurityGeneralHow can I get my name removed from the mailing listHow do I change any details storedContact usThe purpose of this statement is to set out how we use personal information that we may obtain about you. By either registering as a user on this website and by using the Ormsby of Scarisbrick Ltd website generally you agree to this use.Use of your Personal Information1.When you register and use this site:You will be asked to provide certain information such as your contact details. We will store this data and hold it on computers or otherwise. We will use this data to fulfil our agreement with you2.We may use information that you provide or that is obtained by us:a. To register you with our website b. For assessment and analysis (e.g. Market, customer and product analysis) to enable us to review, develop and improve the services which we offer and through our marketing programme. We may use your information to make decisions about you using computerised technology, for example automatically selecting products or services which we think will interest you from the information we have. We may keep you informed of such products and services (including special offers, discounts, offers and so on by any of the following methods:* email* telephone* post* fax* or otherwisewhich we consider may be of interest to you. (If you do not wish Ormsby of Scarisbrick Ltd to supply information of such products and services, please tick the opt-out box provided when registering on this website).3.We may supplement the information that you provide to us with information that we receive from third parties.Fraud Prevention4. In order to protect our customers and us from fraud and theft, we may pass on informationthat we obtain from making identity checks and other information in our customer records, including how you conduct your account, to other retailers and to financial and other organisations (including law enforcement agencies) involved in fraud prevention and detection, to use in the same way.Disclosure of Your Information5.We may give information about you to the following, who may use it for the same purposeas set out above:a. agents who (on our behalf) profile your data so that we may tailor the goods we offer to your specific needs:b. to anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our agreement with you;c. if we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do soSecurity6.We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose on-line. You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing on-line over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default.General7.You have the right to see personal data (as defined in the Data Protection Act) that we keep about you, upon receipt of a written request and payment of a fee. If you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect, please contact us (see details below)8.Please be aware that our site may link to other websites which may be accessed through our site. We are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or the content of these linked websites.How can I get my name removed from the ormsby.co.uk mailing list?If you want to be removed from our mailing list, please send an email to info@ormsby.co.uk with the word ‘remove’ in the subject line and email address that you wish to be removed within the email. Please note that it may take up to 28 days to action your request. How do I change any details stored on ormsby.co.uk?To change any of your registered details on ormsby.co.uk, click on ‘log in & registration’ and enter your login name and password. Once logged in change any of the details shown and click ‘update my details’.For further information about shopping on ormsby.co.uk please read our Terms and ConditionsContact usIf you have any comments or queries in connection with our privacy policy, please email us @info@ormsby.co.uk or call + 44 (0) 1704 880294 or write to Ormsby of Scarisbrick Ltd, Woodland Works, 542 Southport Road, Scarisbrick, Ormskirk, Lancs, L40 9QQ.
Our Products
MENUMENUHomeShop
Product Search
Search for:
Search for:
Search for:
Search for:
Search
Cart
About UsMeet the TeamContact UsMy accountView Cart
* All prices include VAT where appropriate
Ormsby of Scarisbrick, 542 Southport Road, Scarisbrick, Ormskirk, Lancashire L40 9QQ | T. (01704) 880294 | E. info@ormsby.co.uk
